<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="ru"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="ru" /><updated>2024-04-23T11:56:54+00:00</updated><id>https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Выпечка Rumsey</title><subtitle>Наше меню включает в себя разнообразную выпечку по американскому рецепту:  печенье, брауни, кексы и другие кондитерские изделия, приготовленные нами,  вместе с настоящим американцем из Южной Каролины!</subtitle><author><name>Rumsey Cookies</name></author><entry><title type="html">Chocolate Chip Cookies (печенье с кусочками шоколада)</title><link href="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%87%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%8C%D0%B5/2024/04/18/chocolate_chip_cookie.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chocolate Chip Cookies (печенье с кусочками шоколада)" /><published>2024-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%87%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%8C%D0%B5/2024/04/18/chocolate_chip_cookie</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%87%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%8C%D0%B5/2024/04/18/chocolate_chip_cookie.html"><![CDATA[<!-- ![Chocolate Chip Cookies](/assets/images/banners/cookiestack_milk.JPG) -->

<p>Печенье с кусочками шоколада по американскому рецепту.</p>]]></content><author><name>Rumsey Cookies</name></author><category term="печенье" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Почему наши рецепты так отличаются от других рецептов?</title><link href="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D1%80%D0%B5%D1%86%D0%B5%D0%BF%D1%82%D1%8B/2024/04/16/why-are-our-recipes-different.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Почему наши рецепты так отличаются от других рецептов?" /><published>2024-04-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D1%80%D0%B5%D1%86%D0%B5%D0%BF%D1%82%D1%8B/2024/04/16/why-are-our-recipes-different</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rumseycookies.github.io/jekyll-theme-yat/%D1%80%D0%B5%D1%86%D0%B5%D0%BF%D1%82%D1%8B/2024/04/16/why-are-our-recipes-different.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="bringing-our-recipes-to-life">Bringing our recipes to life</h2>

<blockquote>
  <p>“A recipe has no soul. You as the cook must bring soul to the recipe.”
– Thomas Keller</p>
</blockquote>

<p>We take immense pride in crafting each delectable treat with love, passion, and the time-honored traditions of a family business. Our recipes are not just a collection of ingredients and instructions; they are the essence of our family’s love for cooking, passed down through generations. If we wouldn’t eat it, we wouldn’t feed it to anyone! In this post, we would like to share why our recipes outshine those from other companies and factories.</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p><strong>The Heart of a Family Business</strong>: As a family-owned and operated company, we pour our hearts and souls into every batch of cookies, cakes, and pastries we create. This personal touch is something that cannot be replicated in large-scale factories, where mass production often sacrifices the quality and care that comes from a family-driven business.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Cooking with Passion</strong>: For us, baking is not just a job; it’s our passion. Our recipes are the result of countless hours spent in the kitchen, experimenting, and perfecting each dish. This unwavering commitment to excellence ensures that every bite you take is infused with the love and dedication we put into our craft.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Bringing Food to Life</strong>: We believe that cooking is an art form, and our recipes are our canvas. We take great care in selecting the finest ingredients to ensure that each dish is a true reflection of our love for food. Our creations are not merely edible; they are an experience that brings people together, evoking memories and emotions through the power of taste.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Quality Over Quantity</strong>: As a small family business, we prioritize the quality of our products over the quantity we produce. This means that we take the time to perfect each recipe and ensure that every item leaving our kitchen meets our high standards. In contrast, larger companies often prioritize speed and efficiency over the quality and craftsmanship that our family recipes embody. This can result in a less satisfying and authentic culinary experience for those who appreciate the artistry and care that goes into creating a truly exceptional dish.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Embracing Tradition</strong>: Our family recipes have been passed down through generations, each one holding a special place in our hearts. We cherish these time-honored traditions and are committed to preserving them for future generations. By choosing our baked goods, you become a part of our family legacy, enjoying the same delicious treats that have brought joy to our families for years.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>A Taste of Community</strong>: When you choose our baked goods, you’re not only enjoying a superior product; you’re also supporting local businesses and fostering a sense of community.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<p>In conclusion, our heartfelt approach to baking sets us apart from other companies and factories. Our family recipes, born from passion and nurtured through generations, bring a unique depth of flavor and love to every dish we create. When you taste our baked goods, you’re not just enjoying a delicious treat; you’re experiencing the warmth and care of a family business that truly cares about the art of cooking and the joy it brings to your table. Thank you for choosing Выпечка Rumsey to be a part of your culinary journey.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/trio_milk.JPG" alt="trio" /></p>]]></content><author><name>Rumsey Cookies</name></author><category term="рецепты" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing our recipes to life]]></summary></entry></feed>